{
    "id": "cdedaa3c4fdd4188b975dc60e5738da7",
    "title": "Question Tags Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "You are the new secretary, ………………………..?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are you",
                "aren't you",
                "were you"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "665d1274e07042198f1d3c3605f881a7"
        },
        {
            "question": "The meeting is at four o’clock, ………………………………?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is it",
                "isn't it",
                "has it"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b4aa2c94f8eb49bb802aa40aa5c9b3b8"
        },
        {
            "question": "You didn’t meet him, ……………………………….?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "didn't you",
                "did you"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ffd49ba3a5894821876351594999cc6d"
        },
        {
            "question": "You like flowers, ………………………………..?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do you",
                "don't you"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d7129e20b06449ed92bbc96e3e79d60b"
        },
        {
            "question": "You haven’t seen my keys, ……………………………….?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have you",
                "haven't you",
                "had you"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "88194715627e4b9695476d56c62181ed"
        },
        {
            "question": "Harry gave you a gift, ………………………………..?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "does he",
                "did he",
                "didn't he"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "28c8996c70a246bf9f67989cca5c3c12"
        },
        {
            "question": "Let’s have a party, ……………………………….?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "shall we",
                "can we",
                "should we"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "bd1012623f464b5ea2291c0a896fc294"
        },
        {
            "question": "There aren’t any problems, ……………………………?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "are there",
                "aren't there",
                "don't there"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "20bc564acb07488c8d88e1b7b263625a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Nothing can happen, ……………………….?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "can nothing",
                "can it",
                "can't it"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0deec5de8a99426eb5e7a6e6f1154b42"
        },
        {
            "question": "Nobody phoned, ………………………….?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "did they",
                "didn't they",
                "had they"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "45528b4b890b4065a53ec9b9b8479d62"
        }
    ]
}